How cute.
What's it called?
They?
-Ah, Lili. -Private.
Hello, Lili. Where's Lili? Where's Lili?
Here's Lili.
-She's a... -A beauty.
Oh, we are truly beautiful. We are truly beautiful.
-Congratulations. -Well, actually, it's from my daughter.
-Oh, I thought it was yours. -No, what do you think? It's my daughter's.
You're too young to be a grandmother. But how wonderful that you take care of her.
while she's working, I imagine.
Uh, no. I actually just dropped her off at school.
Ah, ok, yes.
And I had to remove her doll because she can't concentrate.
Primary school is not easy.
Elementary school? Well, how old is she?
Seven.
Wow, sorry, sorry. It's just that...
Wow, I didn't know a seven-year-old could...
You do know she's a doll, right?
Of course I know it's a doll.
A little doll. Oh, what's up.
What's up with that nose? Oh, uh, I'm going to eat it.
-Oh, I'm going to eat that nose. -Yeah, I mean, what I mean
-It's just a baby. -Oh, yeah.
-It's a nenuco. -In my generation they called it
"indigo children", and then I think they started calling them
-"crystal generation." Oh, I don't know. -Ah.
They always have like a nickname.
-Can I carry it? A little bit. -Sure.
Hey, watch out.
Oh, grandma is a little violent, isn't she?
Oh, oh, what beautiful eyes she has. She's hot. She's gorgeous.
It's a little heavy, though.
I imagine you're still breastfeeding, right?
Hey, it's a doll.
The thing is, Grandma is very proud of you.
-The father? Present? -My daughter's father?
-No, Lili's dad. -Sorry, which dad are you referring to?
That's a bummer. Of course, they're all the same.
He's missing out. Because these are the best years.
Oh, that smells so good. I can already feel the oxytocin.
Do you like animals?
Because here I have...
a woof woof.
Come, Timothy. Come, come here. We have a new friend.
Her name is Lili. And she's a baby.
Oh, I think Lili liked it. He's very shy.
It's just that I found it abandoned. And I feel like, I don't know...
I feel like he must have suffered a lot because... and he was traumatized.
Well, he hardly barks.
You mean that stuffed dog?
Everyone says that.
It's beautiful. It's good, good.
I'm telling you, he barely barks, he doesn't poop. No.
-Hey, can I borrow it? -Oh, careful.
How cute she is too, huh?
He didn't deny anything when you did that to him.
-Well, well... -Detached, yes, right?
-It goes like with anyone else. -Yes, because it's an inanimate object.
It's a toy baby, it's a doll.
It's a petroleum derivative in the shape of a child. It's made of cloth.
It's made of rubber, look. It doesn't feel. It has no life, it doesn't cry. It doesn't swim.
-Hey! Hey! -Nothing, look. See?
-Do something, for God's sake! For God's sake! -Why?
Because it's a fucking toy, crazy!
For God's sake, do something, she's killing the baby!
Taxi! Taxi!
Police! Call the DIF! Do something! Aren't you going to do anything? It's a baby!
Fucking sick society. Let's go, Timothy. Let's go.
Timothy. Do you really want to poop now or what?
Let's go now. You do the housework.
How wonderful.
These dolls today are already made identical to babies, aren't they?
How much does one like this cost?
Where do they make them, in China, in Taiwan?
-What are you doing? -Oh, what's wrong with you? You wicked woman!
You would be ashamed to walk through life with those sinister dolls.
Women who don't want to be mothers...